const FinalGirlQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Who was the final girl in the first 'Scream' movie?",
        answers: [
                'Tatum',
                'Casey Becker',
                'Sydney Prescott',
                'Angela Barry' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Sydney Prescott'
      },
    {
        question: "Who was the final girl in the first 'Friday the 13th' (1980) movie?",
        answers: [
                'Annie Phillips',
                'Marcie Stanler',
                'Alice Hardy',
                'Brenda Jones' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Alice Hardy'
      },
    {
        question: "Who was the final girl in the first 'Nightmare on Elm Street' (1984) movie?",
        answers: [
                'Nancy Thompson',
                'Tina Gray',
                'Marge Thompson',
                'Kristen Parker' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Nancy Thompson'
      },
    {
        question: "Who was the final girl in the 2005 movie 'The Descent'?",
        answers: [
                'Juno Kaplan',
                'Sarah Carter',
                "Beth O'Brien",
                'Rebecca Vernet' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Sarah Carter'
      },
    {
        question: "Who was the final girl in the 2017 movie 'Happy Death Day'?",
        answers: [
                'Becky Shepard',
                'Lori Spengler',
                "Danielle Bouseman",
                'Tree Gelbman' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Tree Gelbman'
      },
    {
        question: "Who was the final girl in the 1974 release of 'The Texas Chain Saw Massacre'?",
        answers: [
                'Toni Leder',
                'Luda Mae',
                "Sally Hardesty",
                'Pam Sawyer' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Sally Hardesty'
      },
    {
        question: "Who was the final girl in the 2011 movie 'You're Next'?",
        answers: [
                'Aubrey Davison',
                'Erin Harson',
                "Talia Harson",
                'Aimee Davison' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Erin Harson'
      },
    {
        question: "Who was the final girl in the 1974 movie 'Black Christmas'?",
        answers: [
                'Clare Harrison',
                'Barb Kiddor',
                "Jess Bradford",
                'Phyl Martin' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Jess Bradford '
      },
    {
        question: "Who was the final girl in the 1977 version of 'Suspiria'?",
        answers: [
                'Sara Simms',
                'Suzy Bannion',
                'Olga Ivanova',
                'Anke Meier' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Suzy Bannion'
      },
    {
        question: "Who was the final girl in the 1978 version of 'Halloween'?",
        answers: [
                'Lynda Van Der Klok',
                'Annie Brakett',
                'Laurie Strode',
                'Lindsey Wallace' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Laurie Strode'
      },
]